dickies.com 2006-06-19

# Dickies® ~ Privacy Policy

| 

PRIVACY STATEMENT OF WILLIAMSON-DICKIE MFG. CO.

INFORMATION ABOUT OUR ORGANIZATION AND WEB SITE  
Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like Williamson-Dickie Mfg. Co.

Our principal activity is: APPAREL MANUFACTURER

Our privacy policy covers Williamson-Dickie Mfg. Co. and its Web site.

ORGANIZATION NAME  
WILLIAMSON-DICKIE MFG. CO.  
| Address: | 509 W. Vickery Blvd.  
---|---  
City, Zip: | Fort Worth, 76104  
State: | Texas  
Country: | USA  
Controller: | Director e-Business  
Web Site(s): | www.dickies.com  
  
PROVIDING VISITORS WITH ANONYMOUS ACCESS  
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. You must provide certain personal data if you choose to place an order through this web site.

THE SERVICES AND LINKS OF OUR WEB SITE  
Our Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others but does include links to other web sites.

AUTOMATIC COLLECTION OF INFORMATION  
We automatically log data regarding your site visit through the use of cookies. We do not link personal information to cookies. We utilize cookies for the following purposes:

  * Technical administration of the Web site 
  * Customer administration 
  * We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.

DATA COLLECTION AND PURPOSE SPECIFICATION 

  * We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while completing a contest or survey form on this web site 
  * We collect and store personal information that is required to process orders placed on this web site 
  * We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. 
  * The primary purpose of collecting use personal data is for verifying and validating information collected during the shopping process and for awarding contest prizes. If you provide permission for us to contact you via email, you may receive promotional advertising and/or requests for feedback. 
  * Your personal data will not be used for any new purpose without your explicit consent.

CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

  * We do not knowingly collect personal data from children and take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorized the collection of the child's personal data

CONFIDENTIALLY / SECURITY  
We provide a secure SSL transmission method to send us the following types of personal data:

  * primary personal data (such as name and contact details) 
  * identifiers (such as credit card details, Web site password)

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 
  * unauthorized access 
  * improper use or disclosure 
  * unauthorized modification 
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitor's personal data. 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

ACCESS TO THE PERSONAL DATA WE MAY HOLD ABOUT YOU  
Dickies® only maintains personal data required to fulfill orders placed on dickies.com and to award prizes for our contests.

  * Sending an email to [customerservice@dickies.com](mailto:customerservice@dickies.com) and asking whether we are keeping personal data about you. 
  * If we do maintain personal data about you, we will provide a readable copy of the personal data, within approximately 2 weeks from the date of request. (Although we may require proof of your identity prior to releasing the data). 
  * We will provide the information without any charge. 
  * We allow you to modify the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 
    * erased 
    * rectified or amended 
    * completed
  * We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. 
  * We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

**UNSOLICITED IDEA POLICY  
** Williamson-Dickie appreciates individual interest in submitting ideas, proposals, or suggestions. Williamson-Dickie has many projects under development at any given time and it is possible that unsolicited ideas or proposals could be submitted to Williamson-Dickie which are already under consideration or may already be in the planning stages. Williamson-Dickie associates are not authorized to accept or consider unsolicited ideas, suggestions or proposals including ideas for new advertising campaigns, new promotions, new or improved products or technologies, product enhancements, processes, materials, marketing plans or new product names. Please do not send any original creative artwork, suggestions or other works. The sole purpose of this policy is to avoid potential misunderstandings or disputes when Williamson-Dickies’ products or marketing strategies might seem similar to unsolicited ideas submitted to Williamson-Dickie. Please do not send unsolicited ideas, proposals, or suggestions to Williamson-Dickie or anyone at Williamson-Dickie. In the event Williamson-Dickie does receive unsolicited ideas, proposals, or suggestions, regardless of statements which may be made in the correspondence received, the following terms shall apply to all unsolicited idea, proposal, or suggestion submissions.

**TERMS OF IDEA SUBMISSION  
All individuals submitting unsolicited ideas agree to the following:**

**(1) Unsolicited ideas will automatically become the property of Williamson-Dickie, without compensation to individuals making the submission;**

**(2) Williamson-Dickie will be allowed to use the ideas for any purpose and in any way, including providing the unsolicited idea or suggestion to other parties as deemed appropriate.**

PRIVACY SUPPORT   
If you have any further inquires related to this privacy policy, please contact us with your request at [customerservice@dickies.com](mailto:customerservice@dickies.com)

Return  |   Summer Wear  
---  
|   
|   
  What's New in June  
---  
| 

TOP STORIES

2006 Dickies 500 Race for the Riches!  
 [read more ]

TOP STORIES

The nominations are all in!  
 [read more ]

NEWS STAND

"US WEEKLY" and "PEOPLE" both snapped Britney and Kevin in Dickies  
 [read more ]

MUSIC

Trick Daddy in a gray Dickies matched set  
 [read more ]

MOVIES

"The Break Up," starring Jennifer Aniston and Vince Vaughn  
 [read more ]

TV

VH1's "Best Week Ever" Paul Scheer wearing Dickies  
 [read more ]

PauseResume **::** More News

|
